

Oleksandr Brailovskiy

Python Developer Contact

Phone (Telegram, Viber):

+38 050 391 1363

Email: alexander.braylovskiy@gmail.com

Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/olexandr-brailovskyi

GitHub: github.com/NLeech **Address:** Odesa, Ukraine

Skills

Base
 Python, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, SQL

Frameworks and libs Django, Django REST framework, Flask, Flask restful, SQLAlchemy, Celery, Swagger, jQuery, Bootstrap, unittest

- Tools
 PostgreSQL, Docker, AWS, Git, Linux
- Other OOP, SOLID, Patterns

Languages

English - B1 (Intermediate)

Ukrainian - fluent

Russian - native

Summary

I'm a Software Engineer with more than 20 years of commercial experience. I have organizational and problem-solving skills with a high level of self-motivation for work. I am a highly motivated person, willing to work in a team or as an individual worker as well. Seeking to apply my experience and skills to benefit your company as a python developer.

Projects

Weather reminder

GitHub Link

API service for weather forecast notification. **Stack:** Python, HTML, CSS, Django, Django REST framework, Celery, Bootstrap, Postgres, Docker, AWS.

Djangogramm

GitHub Link

A simple Instagram-like application.

Stack: Python, HTML, CSS, Django, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, webpack, Postgres, Docker, AWS.

School management

<u>GitHub</u> Linl

API service for managing students, groups, and courses. **Stack:** Python, Flask, REST API, Flask-restful,

Stack: Python, Flask, REST API, Flask-restful, SQLAlchemy, Swagger, Postgres, Docker, AWS.

Experience

ZEZMAN

Mar 2019 - Present

1C Developer / Team lead

Participate in developing an ERP/CRM system for investment and development holding as a 1C software developer and a team/technical leader.

Agroinvest group

Nov 2015 - Jan 2019

1C Developer / Team lead

Participated in developing an ERP system for an agroindustrial holding as a 1C software developer and a team/technical lead.

Abis-Soft

Oct 1999 - Nov 2015

1C Developer / Team lead

Participated in many projects for the development and implementation of ERP and CRM systems based on 1C as a 1C software developer and team/tech lead.

Education

• **FoxmindEd**May 2022 - Dec 2022

Python back-end development, mentoring.

Odesa National Polytechnic University

Sep 1993 - Jun 1997

Bachelor's degree, Computer science